

ADRIAN MORES

ARCHITECT | MASTER PLUMBER WEB DEVELOPER LAS PIÑAS CITY, METRO MANILA

ABOUT ME

I am an architect with 5 years of experience in designing and managing condominium and subdivision projects. I also do freelance architecture and plumbing design.

Aside from designing spaces suitable for human habitation, I also design websites that suits the client's needs. I design websites with UI/UX as top consideration – much like how architects consider the looks and the user experience when designing spaces.

INDUSTRY SKILLS

























CONTACT ME

+63 927 857 8197
mores.adr@gmail.com
/in/adrianmores
@adrian.taay
@tadaoandoy
@adrian.taay

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Development Projects

Abonado: A Chip-In Tracking App October 2023

This app tracks each participant's contributions (or 'chip-ins') for a specific event and later ensures equal payments. It also provides information about participants who still owe money and tracks whether or not they have made their payments. Stacks used: HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB

Mathle Memory: A Memory and Math Game September 2023

Each round has 3 boxes of different colors containing a digit. Color of the box has an equivalent multiplication factor. Multiply the digit with the color it represents then add all of it before the time runs out.

Stacks used: HTML, CSS, Vanilla JavaScript

Amaia Land Corp.

Project Architect Associate Manager Mar 2023 - Present

I am currently handling all Western Visayas projects, along with one high-rise condominium located in Cubao, Manila.

Project Architect Specialist Mar 2021 – Feb 2023

Handled mid-rise condominium and some subdivision projects in Western Visayas. I then took over the department's initiative to add Smart Home devices to the homes/units the company sells.

Project Architect Senior Associate Feb 2019 – Feb 2021

After passing the board exam, I went back to the same company to continue where I left off. I attended meetings to collaborate with engineers to resolve future conflicts that will arise during construction. I also started organization

Project Intern Architect Feb 2017 - Nov 2018

Assisted the project architect in preparing architectural plans, checking construction plans for conflicts, helped in initiating the study of in-housing the formworks design and implementation. Started the schematic design of Amaia's 16-storey project in Bacolod, Amaia Steps Two Capitol Central.

EDUCATION

<u>Uplift Code Camp</u>

Full Stack Web Development July 2023 – Dec 2023

Attended a boot camp that teaches HTML, CSS, JS, and the MERN Stack.

Adamson University

BS Architecture Nov 2010 – Nov 2016

Learned building design, building utilities, CAD, basic costing, working with teams.